Guide to the Communist Party of the United States of America Audio Collection TAM.132.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Audio Cassette Tapes: Meetings, Bulk, 1978-1989; 1966 - 1999
  - Subseries III:A: National
    - Mid-Term Conference. Youth Workshop. Chicago, IL. Tape 1 *, Sep 18, 1993-Sep 19, 1993 (Box 48, Cassette 2073)
    - Mid-Term Conference. Youth Workshop. Chicago, IL. Tape 2, Sep 18, 1993-Sep 19, 1993 (Box 48, Cassette 2074)
    - Afro-American Committee Meeting. James Steele, Report on the Congressional Black Caucus Legislative Weekend (Washington, DC, Sep 26, 1980 - Sep 28, 1980)., Oct 3, 1980 (Box 43, Cassette 3101)
    - Afro-American Committee Meeting. James Steele, Report on the Congressional Black Caucus Legislative Weekend (Washington, DC, Sep 26, 1980 - Sep 28, 1980)., Oct 3, 1980 (Box 43, Cassette 3102)
    - Afro-American Committee Meeting. Henry Winston on South Africa / Tony Monteiro. Tape 1, Mar 27, 1981 (Box 36, Cassette 840)
    - Afro-American Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Mar 27, 1981 (Box 36, Cassette 841)
    - Afro-American Committee Meeting. Chicago, IL, Aug 1997 (Box 33, Cassette 2489)
    - Anti-Zionist Committee Meeting, Georgia Jewish Community, undated (Box 33, Cassette 2490)
    - Chicano Commission Meeting. Henry Winston, Discussion and Summary. Los Angeles, CA, Apr 28, 1973 (Box 36, Cassette 999)
    - Chicano Commission Meeting. Includes Henry Winston, Lorenzo [Torrez (?)] and "Evy's" [Evalina Alarcon (?)] Youth Report. Los Angeles, CA. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Apr 28, 1973 (Box 36, Cassette 1034)
    - Chicano Commission Meeting. May Day Meeting. Opening and Last Session, Apr 29, 1973 (Box 28, Cassette 1237)
    - Education Committee, Branch Educational. James Steele, Report to the National Council Meeting (Jan 22 - Jan 24), undated (Box 32, Cassette 4935)
    - Health Commission, Apr 26 (Box 49, Cassette 5016)
    - History Commission. Elliot Waxman, Oral History Interview, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4951)
    - Jewish Commission, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2561)
    - Labor Department. Discussion. Tape 1, Apr 26, 1986 (Box 44, Cassette 2543)
    - Labor Department. Discussion. Tape 2, Apr 26, 1986 (Box 44, Cassette 2547)
    - Labor Department. Discussion. Tape 3, Apr 26, 1986 (Box 44, Cassette 2551)
    - Mexican-American Commission Report, undated (Box 49, Cassette 5015)
    - Native American Commission. Tape 1, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2583)
    - Native American Commission. Tape 2. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 44, Cassette 2584)
    - Native American Commission. The Hopi, Industrial Society and the National Question [Tape 1 (?)], Oct 15, 1980 (Box 43, Cassette 3108)
    - Native American Commission. The Hopi, Discussion. Tape 2, Oct 15, 1980 (Box 43, Cassette 3109)
    - Native American Commission. The Hopi, Discussion. Tape 3, Oct 15, 1980 (Box 43, Cassette 3110)
    - Native American Commission. The Hopi, Discussion. Tape 4, Oct 15, 1980 (Box 32, Cassette 4854)
    - Political [Action (?)] Committee. Meeting. Henry Winston, Speech on Democratic Centralism, Apr 22, 1975 (Box 36, Cassette 1082)
    - Political [Action (?)] Committee. Special Meeting. Henry Winston, Report on National Convention, 21st. Tape 1, Jul 8, 1975 (Box 36, Cassette 994)
    - Political [Action (?)] Committee. Special Meeting. Henry Winston, Report on National Convention, 21st. Tape 2. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jul 8, 1975 (Box 36, Cassette 993)
    - Political Action Commission. Tape 2, Apr 31, 1992 (Box 44, Cassette 2629)
    - Political Action Commission. Opening Report and Discussion. Tape 1, May 31, 1992 (Box 44, Cassette 2626)
    - Political Action Commission. Tape 2, May 31, 1992 (Box 44, Cassette 2627)
    - Political [Action (?)] Commission. Si Gerson, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2628)
    - Recruitment Committee Meeting. James Steele, Report, Apr 11, 1976 (Box 34, Cassette 1620)
    - Religious Commission, Nov 12, 1983 (Box 44, Cassette 2630)
    - Religious Commission, Nov 12, 1983 (Box 44, Cassette 2631)
  - Subseries III:B: District and State
    - [District Committee Meeting (?)]. Ted M. Report. Washington, [DC (?)], Apr 4, 1980 (Box 36, Cassette 940)
    - District Organizers Meeting. Gus Hall and Victor Perlo. Tape 1, Sep 18, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 1992)
    - District Organizers Meeting. Economic Discussion. Tape 2, Sep 18, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 1991)
    - District Organizers Meeting. Gus Hall on Elections. Tape 3, Sep 18, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 1964)
    - District Organizers Meeting. Gus Hall. New Tactics on Elections, Sep 18, 1984 (Box 42, Cassette 2755)
    - East Coast Regional Meeting. Includes Henry Winston and Pat Barile, Aug 20, 1977 (Box 36, Cassette 1058)
    - [Illinois (?) District Meeting], [1971 (?)] (Box 44, Cassette 2639)
    - Illinois Section Convention. Gus Hall, Two Speeches, 1972 (Box 30, Cassette 1562)
    - Illinois Section Convention, Nov 23, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1626)
    - [Illinois Section Convention]. Tape 1, [Nov 23, 1974] (Box 34, Cassette 1628)
    - Illinois Section Convention. Tape 2, Nov 23, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1629)
    - Illinois Section Convention. Tape 3, Nov 23, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1627)
    - [Illinois Section Convention (?)], [Nov 23, 1974] (Box 34, Cassette 1630)
    - [Illinois Section Convention (?)], [Nov 23, 1974] (Box 34, Cassette 1631)
    - [Michigan (?)] State Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, The All-People's Front, Mar 18, 1985 (Box 36, Cassette 1013)
    - New York State Club (?) Meeting. Gus Hall, Mar 1, 1982 (Box 42, Cassette 2711)
    - New York State Committee Meeting. Si Gerson, Report on 1982 Elections. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Nov 14, 1982 (Box 36, Cassette 1051)
    - New York State Committee Meeting. Jarvis Tyner, Report, Jun 2, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1879)
    - New York State Committee Meeting, Nov 16, 1985 (Box 36, Cassette 983)
    - New York State Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Jun 26, 1987 (Box 36, Cassette 1047)
    - New York State Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Jun 26, 1987 (Box 36, Cassette 1045)
    - New York State Committee Meeting. Political Action, Dec 19, 1987 (Box 45, Cassette 1885)
    - New York State Committee Meeting. Report. Tape 2, Feb 6, 1988 (Box 45, Cassette 1934)
    - [New York] State Committee Meeting. Jarvis Tyner on U.S.S.R. Tape 2, undated (Box 45, Cassette 1932)
    - New York State Communist Party Meeting. Gus Hall, On 22nd National Convention. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jun 23, 1979 (Box 48, Cassette 2114)
    - New York State Convention. Sides 6 and 7, Apr 20, 1969 (Box 45, Cassette 1874)
    - New York State Convention. Sides 8 and 9, Apr 20, 1969 (Box 45, Cassette 1870)
    - New York State Convention, 22nd. Gus Hall, Jun 23, 1979 (Box 45, Cassette 1909)
    - New York State Convention, 22nd. Gus Hall, Jun 23, 1979 (Box 42, Cassette 2729)
    - New York State Convention. Jarvis Tyner, Report. Tape 1, Apr 17, 1982 (Box 45, Cassette 1869)
    - New York State Convention. Workshop on Women's Equality. Tape 1, Feb 19, 1983 (Box 36, Cassette 1091)
    - New York State Convention, 23rd. Henry Winston, Oct 9, 1983 (Box 45, Cassette 1857)
    - New York State Convention. Jarvis Tyner, Report. Tape 1, Jun 26, 1987 (Box 36, Cassette 1048)
    - New York State Convention. Plenary. Tape 5, Jun 27, 1987 (Box 36, Cassette 981)
    - New York State Convention. Jarvis Tyner, Report, Jun 28, 1987 (Box 36, Cassette 982)
    - New York State Convention. Jarvis Tyner and Alva Buxenbaum, Alternative Report, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2620)
    - New York State Convention. Gus Hall, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2621)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 1 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1940)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 1, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1978)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 1, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2044)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 2 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1941)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 2, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1985)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 2. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2043)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 3 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1942)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 3, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1987)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 3, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2042)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 4 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1943)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 4, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1988)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 4. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2041)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 5 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1950)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 5, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1986)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 5, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2040)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 6 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1949)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 6, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1977)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 6, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2039)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 7 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1948)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 7, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1976)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 7, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2052)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 8 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1946)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 8, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1975)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 8, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2051)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 9 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1947)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 9, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1984)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 9, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2050)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 10 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1945)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 10, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1983)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 10, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2049)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 11 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1944)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 11, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1982)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 11, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2048)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 12 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1956)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 12, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1980)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 12, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2047)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 13 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1955)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 13, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1958)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 13, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1970)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 14 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1954)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 14, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1979)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 14, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2046)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 15 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1953)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 15, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1972)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 15, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 2045)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 16 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1952)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 16, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1957)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 16, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1971)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 17 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1951)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 17 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1959)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 17, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1981)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 18 *, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1961)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 18, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1963)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 18, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1974)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 20, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1960)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 20, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1962)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 20, Oct 25, 1991 (Box 39, Cassette 1973)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 21 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2618)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 22 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2617)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 23 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2616)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 24 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2615)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 25 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2614)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 26 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2613)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 27 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2612)
    - New York State Convention. Tape 28 *, Nov 10, 1991 (Box 44, Cassette 2611)
    - New York State Convention. Gus Hall, Jun 13, 1992 (Box 44, Cassette 2622)
    - New York State Convention (?). [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jun 7 (Box 45, Cassette 1875)
    - New York State Convention. Workshop on Women's Equality. Tape 1. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 36, Cassette 1090)
    - New York State Convention. Workshop on Women's Equality. Tape 1, undated (Box 45, Cassette 1903)
    - New York State District Election Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 1, Apr 4, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2004)
    - New York State District Election Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 2, Apr 4, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2003)
    - New York State District Membership Meeting. Tape 1, Jun 9, 1990 (Box 44, Cassette 2588)
    - New York State District Membership Meeting. Tape 2, Jun 9, 1990 (Box 44, Cassette 2589)
    - New York State District Membership Meeting. Tape 3, Jun 9, 1990 (Box 44, Cassette 2590)
    - New York State District Membership Meeting. Gus Hall, May 24, 1993 (Box 39, Cassette 2000)
    - New York State District Membership Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 1 *, May 24, 1993 (Box 44, Cassette 2586)
    - New York State District Membership Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 2, Jun 24, 1993 (Box 44, Cassette 2587)
    - Regional Conference. Henry Winston, Oct 14, 1973 (Box 36, Cassette 1095)
    - South West Regional Conference. Unidentified Discussion on Work in Locals. Tape 4, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4904)
    - State Committee Meeting. Ben Davis, After 16th National Convention, Jul 19, 1959 (Box 48, Cassette 2105)
    - State Committee Meeting, Jun 26, 1977 (Box 45, Cassette 1878)
    - State Committee Meeting. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 24, 1981 (Box 36, Cassette 1115)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Jan 9, 1982 (Box 36, Cassette 1022)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Jan 9, 1982 (Box 36, Cassette 1021)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 3. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 9, 1982 (Box 36, Cassette 1020)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Mar 13, 1982 (Box 45, Cassette 1908)
    - State Committee Meeting. Jarvis Tyner, Report. Tape 1, Feb 19, 1983 (Box 36, Cassette 1116)
    - State Committee Meeting. Includes Jarvis Tyner, Irving H (?). and Kevin Lynch. Tape 2, Jul 9, 1983 (Box 45, Cassette 1918)
    - State Committee Meeting. Includes Jarvis Tyner, Bill Davis, Kevin Mercadel and Kevin Lynch, Jul 9, 1983 (Box 45, Cassette 1902)
    - State Committee Meeting. Jarvis Tyner and Hector (?). Tape 4, Jul 10, 1983 (Box 45, Cassette 1929)
    - State Committee Meeting. Jarvis Tyner [Discussing Black Capitalism], Mar 21, 1987 (Box 44, Cassette 2650)
    - State Committee Meeting. Jarvis Tyner. Report, Mar 21, 1987 (Box 36, Cassette 1043)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Mar 21, 1987 (Box 45, Cassette 1906)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 5. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], May 9, 1987 (Box 36, Cassette 1044)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Sep 16, 1989 (Box 39, Cassette 2011)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 4, Sep 22, 1990 (Box 39, Cassette 1997)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Sep 7, 1991 (Box 45, Cassette 1928)
    - State Committee Meeting, Oct 5, 1991 (Box 45, Cassette 1917)
    - State Committee Meeting, Oct 20, 1991 (Box 45, Cassette 1931)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 3 (?), Oct 20, 1991 (Box 45, Cassette 1877)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 4, Oct 20, 1991 (Box 45, Cassette 1887)
    - State Committee Meeting. Saturday Session. Includes Larry Moscowitz. Tape 3, May 9-May 10 (Box 45, Cassette 1886)
    - State Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Aug 3 (Box 45, Cassette 1884)
    - State Committee Meeting. Discussion on South Africa. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 45, Cassette 1907)
    - State Convention. Discussion on Racism, Mar 27, 1971 (Box 45, Cassette 1871)
    - Unidentified District Meeting. Discussion, Includes Bill, Aaron and Ben, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4844)
    - [West Coast / South West Regional Conference], undated (Box 44, Cassette 2644)
    - Wisconsin Conference. Gus Hall, 1968 (Box 30, Cassette 1586)
    - Wisconsin Conference. Gus Hall, Party Building, 1968 (Box 30, Cassette 1585)
  - Subseries III:C: Youth
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Opening Plenary Session and James Steele, Keynote Address. Tape 1, Apr 29, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3365)
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Plenary Continued, and Workshop Reports. Tape 2, Apr 29, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3366)
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Plenary Continued, Workshop Reports, and International Guests. Tape 3, Apr 29, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3367)
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Plenary Continued. Tape 4, Apr 29, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3368)
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Tape 5, Apr 29, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3369)
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Gus Hall, Speech, Apr 30, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3370)
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Gus Hall, Rally against Reaganism. Cleveland, OH, Apr 30, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3371)
    - Young Communist League Founding Convention. Final Plenary Session, May 1, 1983 (Box 54, Cassette 3372)
    - Young Communist League. National Convention, 2nd. Boston Theater Group. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jun 27, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1882)
    - Young Communist League. National Convention, 2nd. Includes John Bechtel, Corrina (?), Komsomol Representative and WFDY [World Federation of Democratic Youth] Representative, Jun 27, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1927)
    - Young Communist League. National Convention, 2nd. Tape 1, Jun 28, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1904)
    - Young Communist League. National Convention, 3rd. Education in the YCL. Part 3, Jun 18, 1988 (Box 49, Cassette 3688)
    - [Young Communist League ?] Meeting. Discussion of Political Dispute, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4808)
    - [Young Communist League?] 1, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2649)
    - [Young Communist League?] 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4820)
    - [Young Communist League?] 3, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4821)
    - [Young Communist League?] 4, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4207)
    - [Young Communist League?] 5, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4920)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. Bicentennial. Recruitment Committee Meeting. Includes Henry Winston. Tape 1, Nov 19, 1975 (Box 36, Cassette 1079)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Council Meeting. James Steele, Feb 1, 1982 (Box 47, Cassette 2202)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention. Labor Workshop. Tape 1, [circa 1974] (Box 34, Cassette 1651)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention. Labor Workshop. Tape 2, [circa 1974] (Box 34, Cassette 1652)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention, 3rd. Tape 1, undated (Box 28, Cassette 1186)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Conference. Gus Hall, Jan 10, 1981-Jan 13, 1981 (Box 44, Cassette 2633)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention, 5th. Opening and First Plenary Session. Tape 1, Jun 27, 1981 (Box 44, Cassette 2636)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention, 5th. First and Second Plenary Sessions. Tape 2, Jun 27, 1981 (Box 44, Cassette 2637)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention, 5th. James Steele, Keynote Address; Gus Hall, Speech; Antar Mberi, Poems, Jun 27, 1981 (Box 44, Cassette 2634)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention, 5th. Gus Hall, James Steele and Antar Mberi, Jun 27, 1981 (Box 45, Cassette 1921)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention, 5th. Gus Hall, Jun 27, 1981 (Box 44, Cassette 2635)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. Conference, Café (?), Sounds of Freedom, Aug 15, 1981 (Box 45, Cassette 1935)
    - Young Workers Liberation League. National Convention. Speech by Gus Hall and Poems by Anaar Mberi, undated (Box 42, Cassette 2726)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. (?) Ernestine, Youth Rights. Tape 1 *, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1702)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1709)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1708)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Tape 4, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1707)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1706)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Tape 6, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1705)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Rogue Report on Convention. Tape 7, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1704)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Busing Report. Tape 8, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1703)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Side 9, Side A. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1710)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Bsoton Discussion. Tape 9, Side B, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1701)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Jarvis Tyner, Report on Leadership. Tape 10, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1700)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Tape 11, Oct 26, 1974-Oct 28, 1974 (Box 34, Cassette 1699)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Matty Berkelhammer, Opening Remarks and James Steele, Youth Rights, Aug 2, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1639)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. James Steele, Youth Rights. Tape 2, Aug 2, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1602)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Discussion of James Steele's Report. Tape 3, Aug 2, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1596)
    - Young Workers Liberation League / Central Committee Meeting. Discussion of James Steele's Report and Jill (?)'s Report. Tape 4, Aug 2, 1975 (Box 34, Cassette 1595)